Michael mss. LMC 2996
Lilly Library
- Playbills
  - Risk and Reward; Robert Caisley; Phoenix Theatre Indianapolis, 2017 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rivals, The; Richard Brinsley Sheridan; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - River Niger, The; Joseph Walker; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Road to Mecca, The; Athol Fugard; Lyttleton Theatre, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rock of Ages; Chris D'Arienzo; IU Auditorium, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rock 'n' Roll; Tom Stoppard; Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Romans in Britain, The; Howard Brenton; National Theatre, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Romeo et Juliette; Prokofiev; Theatre National de L'Opera, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Romulus the Great; Friedrich Durrenmatt; Staatstheater Kassel, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Roommate, The; Jen Silverman; Ivy Tech Waldron Rose Firebay, 2020 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Roots; Arnold Wesker; Belgrade Theatre Coventry, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Rose Tattoo, The; Tennessee Williams; Martin Beck Theatre, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Rose's Dilemma; Neil Simon; MTC City Center Stage 1, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Rosmersholm; Henrik Ibsen; Court House Theatre (Niagara), 2006 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Ross; Terence Rattigan; Hudson Theatre, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Royal Family, The; Kaufman, Ferber; Samuel J. Friedman Theatre, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Royal Hunt of the Sun, The; Peter Shaffer; ANTA Theatre, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Rules of the Game, The; Luigi Pirandello; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Salad Days; Reynolds, Slade; Vaudeville Theatre, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Scarecrow, The; Percy MacKaye; John F. Kennedy Center, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Scarlet Pimpernel, The; Knighton, Wildhorn; Minskoff Theatre, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - School for Husbands / The Imaginary Cuckold; Moliere; Criterion Center Stage Right, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - School for Scandal, The; Richard Brinsley Sheridan; Det Ny Teater, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - School for Wives; Moliere; Almeida Theatre, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Seagull, The; Anton Chekhov; Walter Kerr Theatre, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Secret Rapture, The; David Hare; Lyttelton Theatre, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Seminar; Theresa Rebeck; Golden Theatre, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Servant to Two Masters, The; Carlo Goldoni; Kennedy Center, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Sexy Laundry; Michele Rimi; Thousand Islands Playhouse, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Shadow of Heroes; Robert Ardrey; Picadilly Theatre, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Shadowlands; William Nicholson; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Shaker Chair, The; Adam Bock; Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Shape of Things, The; Neil LaBute; Promenade Theatre, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - She Loves Me; Masteroff, Bock, Harnick; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - She Stoops to Conquer; Oliver Goldsmith; Queen's Theatre, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Sherlock Holmes; A. Doyle, W. Gillette; Broadhurst Theatre, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Shoemaker's Holiday, The; Thomas Dekker; Theatre National Populaire, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Shot in the Dark, A; Harry Kurnitz; Booth Theatre, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Shrapnel in the Heart; Palmer, Connelly; Famous Door, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Side Man; Warren Leight; John Golden Theatre, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Singin' in the Rain; Kelly, Comden, Green; Oliver Theatre, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Single Spies; Alan Bennett; Lyttelton Theatre, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Sister Mary Ignatius Explains It All For You / The Actor's Nightmare; Christopher Durang; Westside Arts Theatre (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Sisters Rosensweig, The; Wendy Wasserstein; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Sisterly Feelings; Alan Ayckbourn; Oliver Theatre, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Six Degrees of Separation; John Guare; Vivian Beaumont Theater, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Six Persons in Search of an Author; Luigi Pirandello; Det Kongelige Teater, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Skylight; David Hare; Royale Theatre, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Sleeping Beauty; Holland, Austin, Darrell; Bristol Hippodrome, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Smokey Joe's Café; Leiber and Stoller; IU Auditorium, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Sneeze, The; Chekhov, Frayn; Aldwych Theatre, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Snow Geese, The; Sharr White; Samuel J. Friedman Theatre, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Someone Waiting; Emlyn Williams; Dundee Repertory Theatre, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Someone Who'll Watch Over Me; Frank McGuinness; Booth Theatre, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Something Rotten!; Kirkpatric and Kirkpatric; IU Auditorium, 2019 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Souvenir; Stephen Temperley; Schein Performance Hall (Sanibel), 2011 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Spamalot; Idle Du Prez; Shubert Theatre, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Speed the Plow; David Mamet; Royale Theatre, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Spelling Bee; Finn, Sheinkin, Feldman; Circle in the Square Theatre, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Spoils of War; Michael Weller; Music Box, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Spoon River Anthology; Edgar Lee Masters; Belasco Theatre, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Spring Awakening; Sater, Sheik, Wedekind; Eugene O'Neill Theatre, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Stage Directions of Eugene O'Neill; Christopher Loar; Arena Stage, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Staircase; Charles Dyer; Aldwych Theatre, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Starlight Express; Webber, Stilgoe; Apollo Victoria Theatre, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Steel Magnolias; Robert Harling; Lucille Lortel Theatre, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Sticks and Bones; David Rabe; Public Theatre, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Stones in His Pockets; Marie Jones; Duke of York's Theatre, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Streamers; David Rabe; Mitzie E. Newhouse Theater, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Streets of London, The; Dion Boucicault; Her Majesty's Theatre (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Streets of New York, The; Grael, Chodosh; Maidman Playhouse, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Strider; Rozovsky, Mark; Chelsea Theatre Center, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Submariners; Tom McClenaghan; Royal Court Theatre Upstairs, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Sunday in the Park with George; Sondheim, Lapine; Royal George Theatre (Niagara), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Sunset Blvd.; Webber, Black, Hampton; Adelphi Theatre, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Superior Donuts; Tracy Letts; Music Box, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Sweeney Todd; Sondheim, Wheeler; Theatre Royal Drury Lane, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Sweeney Todd; Sondheim, Wheeler; Eugene O'Neill Theatre, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - That Championship Season; Jason Miller; Booth Theatre, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - They're Playing Our Song; Simon, Hamlisch, Sager; Shaftesbury Theatre, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Waitress; Nelson, Bareilles; IU Auditorium, 2021 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Will Rogers Follies, The; Stone, Coleman, Comden; Palace Theatre, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Festivals and Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Donor's inventory (Box 5, Folder 68)